[
    {
       "question":"Where did the narratory of the story 'The Snake of the Mirror' ?",
       "choice1":"Small opened house",
       "choice2": "Small rented house",
       "choice3": "Small gifted house",
       "choice4": "Small pucca house",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What made the noise in the doctor's room?",
       "choice1":"the owls",
       "choice2":"the snakes",
       "choice3":"the rats",
       "choice4":"the pigeon",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"The narrator of the story 'The Snake of the Mirror' was a -",
       "choice1":"Teacher",
       "choice2": "Doctor",
       "choice3": "Farmer",
       "choice4": "Engineer",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"The doctor wants to look -",
       "choice1":"handsome",
       "choice2":"smart",
       "choice3":"grave",
       "choice4":"shy",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"The snake coiled around -",
       "choice1":"the doctor's left arm",
       "choice2": "the doctor's right arm",
       "choice3": "the doctor's left leg",
       "choice4": "the doctor's right leg",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Whom did the doctor wants to marry ?",
       "choice1":"A scientist",
       "choice2":"A teacher",
       "choice3":"A women doctor",
       "choice4":"A singer",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"HOw many times did the doctor hear the sound of rats?",
       "choice1":"Once",
       "choice2": "Twice",
       "choice3": "Thrice",
       "choice4": "Four times",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What is 'Malaria Medica' ?",
       "choice1":"a book",
       "choice2":"a medicine",
       "choice3":"a paper",
       "choice4":"a magazine",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"The second World War was broke out in -",
       "choice1":"1934",
       "choice2": "1935",
       "choice3": "1937",
       "choice4": "1939",
       "answer": 4
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who was the Kalam's science teacher?",
       "choice1":"Ramanatha Shastri",
       "choice2":"Siva Subramania Iyer",
       "choice3":"Sivapakasan",
       "choice4":"None of these",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Who has written the autobiography 'My Childhood' ?",
       "choice1":"Vikram Seth",
       "choice2": "A. P. J. Abdul Kalam",
       "choice3": "Isaac Asimov",
       "choice4": "Deborah Cowley",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Where was A. P. J. Abdul Kalam born?",
       "choice1":"Ramanathpuram",
       "choice2":"Ramachandrapuram",
       "choice3":"Rameswaram",
       "choice4":"Ramapuram",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"A. P. J. Abdul Kalam was born in - ",
       "choice1":"a middle class Tamil family",
       "choice2": "a upper class Telugu family",
       "choice3": "a low grade TAmil family",
       "choice4": "a rich family",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who was Samsuddin?",
       "choice1":"Abdul Kalam's father",
       "choice2":"Abdul Kalam's brother",
       "choice3":"Abdul Kalam's cousin",
       "choice4":"Abdul Kalam's uncle",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Abdul Kalam's father's name was - ",
       "choice1":"Shafiullah",
       "choice2": "Jainulabdeen",
       "choice3": "Kamaluddeen",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What thing did Abdul Kalam use to collect?",
       "choice1":"Mustard seeds",
       "choice2":"Tamarind seeds",
       "choice3":"Linseed",
       "choice4":"None of these",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Abdul Kalam's mother's name was -",
       "choice1":"Ashiamma",
       "choice2": "Dinamani",
       "choice3": "Rukhaiya",
       "choice4": "Begum Akhtar",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"The name of the Tamil news paper distributed by Kalam was - ",
       "choice1":"Dinamani",
       "choice2":"Sentinel",
       "choice3":"Sanmarg",
       "choice4":"Azad Sipahi",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"How old was Kalam when Second World War brokeout ?",
       "choice1":"10 years",
       "choice2": "8 years",
       "choice3": "6 years",
       "choice4": "12 years",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"In which state of India is Rameshwaram?",
       "choice1":"Tamil Nadu",
       "choice2":"Chennai",
       "choice3":"Kerala",
       "choice4":"None of these",
       "answer": 1
   }
   
   
   
   
   ]